<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Lennard Goh</title>
 <link href="http://lennardgoh.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://lennardgoh.github.io/"/>
 <updated>2015-01-15T14:02:06-05:00</updated>
 <id>http://lennardgoh.github.io</id>
 <author>
   <name>Lennard Goh</name>
   <email>lennardgoh@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Hello World</title>
   <link href="http://lennardgoh.github.io//hello-world"/>
   <updated>2015-01-15T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://lennardgoh.github.io/hello-world</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Before this began, I was spoilt for choice as to where I should host this site. Should I revert back to simpler old blogging platforms like wordpress or blogger? Should I build this site from scratch with the limited html and css skills which I have? It would be nice to have the freedom of customization/control of html while still not over-complicating this little project of website which I would like to take up. &lt;a href=&quot;http://pages.github.com&quot;&gt;Github pages&lt;/a&gt; was the clear choice for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have always been a fan of Github and their open source policies. I somehow chanced upon their free Github pages service to host this page for all users. Together with &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://github.com/poole/poole&quot;&gt;Poole&lt;/a&gt;, the whole idea of hosting this site as a bunch of static files on my computer caught my eye. So here are some of the advantages of this system that led to this decision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Since the static files are located on my computer, I can easily work on this site offline and push it to Github once internet access is available.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Entirely free service&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Simple Markdown format for content input means I can focus on the content rather than the html/css&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Beautiful minimalist theme.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far I&amp;#39;m loving this combination of Github pages, Jekyll and poole. I might post a quick tutorial for creating your own static site in the near future if you are interested in creating a site of your own too. Stay tuned.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
